Wow, so many are learning
to become Taoists
lf l had money l'd do that, too
A month back you wanted to be like Li Bai
ln fact you suggested it'd be good
to be like Li Bai
...since he's romantic and has style
Mei Liang
Men aren't allowed here
l'm looking for Mei Liang
Get out
Mei Liang
Get dressed quickly
Mei Liang, Mei Liang...
Mei Liang
Who is this man?
He is the rich husband of Yu Yao Mei
Ever since you left,
all l could think of...
is just you...l...
You filthy man
What are you doing here? Get out
Mei Liang
Wait...my husband yearns for her
day and night
Please let him speak out his heart!
Yes, please!
Thank you for your care over the years...
l'd like to express my profound gratitude
Mei, please return with me
After l've settled my tea business
in Chin Tang
...l'll not leave Chang An again
l promise to be by your side day and night
l can learn composing poems with you
Mei, you ought to know that...
l cannot bear children
To carry on Li family's lineage,
please come with us
Abandoning home for spiritual studies
is wrong maybe;
But l hope you wouldn't force me
l'm not at all compelling you
Please don't say that
Then l can discipline myself in peace
Mei Liang...
There are five commandments in our creed
Firstly, you shall not kill
Yes
Secondly, you shall not drink alcohol
You shall speak the truth
Yes
You shall not steal
Fifth, do not commit adultery
Yes
Should you transgress in any way,
you'll be expelled
Yes
They say you're Chang An's gifted
female scholar
...with an uninhibited & amorous
literary talent
Nothing but frivolous talk l'd say
lndeed modest of you to say so
Regardless of whether it is true
...or if they are rumours
l do not wish to hear more
Yes
Yu Yao Mei, a girl from
Chang An's Li family,
in January of the year of Han Tung,
...becomes a Taoist
The Goddess of Heaven administers rule
...from Quan Lun to the north heavens
lnequity not be purged, till ye die...
Ling Nan lychees generate so much
body heat
Please remind me next time...
not to eat so many
Madam, l've heard that
if soaked in well water...
they're much lighter
The co-existence of
Yin and Yang energies...
Oh, teacher
Of late, Secretary Wang complains
of weak kidneys
You mentioned that mystifying
Yin Yang concentrate
When can it be ready?
Every ingredient is available
What we now lack...
is just a good quality medicinal tripod
Oh, that's no problem at all
l'll give you ten taels of silver
to buy it
Thank you, madam
Yiu Liang...
you are so audacious!
There is a sermon going on inside
...and you should behave yourself
l mean, such blasphemy!
Madam Shie
A sermon could be given any time,
any where
Whenever you wish l could give one
at your home...
Come, look at this
This silk feels really light
Oh, it should be comfortable to wear!
Do you know what kind of silk it is?
lt's the silk from Bok Chau
Right...
Madam Shie
This silk is a royal gift to the court
...and priceless
l asked the councillor to send over
two maids
...to that horny official of Bok Chau
ln return he gave me...
Be careful!
This is really so beautiful and rare!
Look...So pretty...
Look...
Hey, my ear rings!
Fei Hsiang, Wan Yang's ear rings
are so fragrant
Let me take a sniff
Hmm...like some vintage Ge Zuo wine!
Let's play 'find the earrings' shall we?
Okay...
Give it back, you naughty...
You're a Taoist priestess,
yet why wear earrings?
Give it back
Come on, give it to me...
Sister Yuan Gi, you're the host tonight
You should hide the earrings;
l'll be the hunting bird
Alright!
No peeping
l want to be the bird...
No, l'm Wan Fei Hsiang
l can fly, l should be the bird
l've hidden them
Coming
l see. The right foot moves
but the left doesn't
Must be definitely inside the right sock
Really?
Sure
Must be in there
Look
Let's see where they are
You all must be exhausted
Thank you
A breath of nice fragrance!
May l ask who is it?
Just call me Lu Chiao
Thank you
Lu Chiao
So nice of Miss Lu Chiao
Yes...
Well, have you found the ear rings?
Wah Yang,
you didn't take back the earrings,
did you?
What if l did not?
lf you didn't...Well then,
l'll let you ladies treat me as you like
Oh, really? Come
They're here
Where? Where are they hidden?
lt's so refined out here;
Was it out of boredom...
that you came out to seek pleasure
& make merry?
No. Most Taoist priestesses
at the monastery...
are just sycophants of Mandarin officials
l didn't wish to mix with them
Yuan Gi
you should learn more from Wah Yang
You shouldn't have left,
without learning how to perfect...
the pills of immortality
Are the Taoist pills really
that important?
More important than poetry?
Can't necessarily be said so
The reason l joined Taoist sect was to...
become an independent
self-sufficient woman
Well-said!
Come, have a drink
Facing the wind we sigh,
flowers repeatedly fall
Spring returns yet the fragrant
longings don't
These peonies ignored because of
their high price
Their arrogant aroma even
intimidates buterflies
Flowers so deep red must be from
palatial gardens
Leaves so dark green that
dust dare not settle there
The same if transplanted to
the lmperial Gardens
Young lords then wouldn't buy them
without cause
You study classics; What have you learnt?
You know, we've been too licentious
Life is to pursue happiness
Whatever l do, l never repent
Come on, let's tread the mud...
lt's great fun...
We used to do this while ploughing
back home
The farm soil was so loose and soft
Yes. Look, they are playing...
like a bunch of kids
Do you like treading on mud?
As a child l used to do that everyday
Here, everyone. Come have a drink of
mud-wine
Tsui Pok Hau
Yu Yuan Gi
l have heard of you
l haven't heard of you
Well, the Literary genius of Chang An
lt's a shame these few years
l have not had...
the time to read and write
Where do you want me to take you?
Wherever this boat drifts to
From a lover?
A girl whom l used to know as a kid
After l moved apart from her...
she married another man
He was unfaithful and tortured her
She committed suicide with this hairpin...
by piercing her throat
Blood...bleeding for a day and a night
before she died
l killed that man
Blood stain on this gold hairpin
...hasn't come off since then!
Where is it?
Here
Why didn't you choose to be her husband?
Did you let her marry that man...
so you could be a leisurely
and carefree knight?
My friend is waiting for me outside
Duk-Goo Shing Yang, as a military officer
you dared to conspire with Yin Shu...
and assassinate Secretary Cheng Wei Yi
l, Tsui Pok Hau
must kill today an old thief like you
l, sword-maker Auyang,
must behead today a malingerer like you
...for the sake ofjustice
Please don't do that
lt certainly must be lonely up there
Say, if one becomes a celestial being...
would it be very lonesome and adrift?
lf you were to ascend the heavens...
my heart would cry to see you off
And where would you go?
A wanderer is doomed to move about
There'll come a day when he may need
to pause
What happens then?
l'll borrow a girl's body
...over and again
Flowers make poems
Frost make the fairies
Sleep with open curtain
...facing the hill
Well written
You're so learned
Why did you become a Taoist priestess?
What else could an erudite girl do?
Didn't want to be some
rich merchant's wife
Nor wish to be a concubine
Don't prefer being a courtesan
Nor liked being a Buddhist nun
l was reluctant to give up my hair
Only choice left was to be
a Taoist priestess
Why did you chose to be
a gypsy swordsman?
Me?
l don't like being someone's husband
Nor be a high ranking official
l don't prefer being a business man
Nor be some General going about...
annexing territories
lt's mostly these corrupt officials
l can't tolerate
So l can only be a swordsman
Being a man is lucky, l think
One can enjoy benefits of being
a senior official
...or at worst become a wandering
swordsman
Auyang the sword maker
The friend you saw at the riverside
He made this sword
A good friend of yours?
When are you going out to kill again?
When would you come back?
l go on without turning back
l rush in the plains for a long journey,
carrying a sabre and a bow
l never change even if l lose my life
l'm not only sincere but brave
My strong will is inviolable
Though my body perishes,
my soul will stay on
Even as a ghost l remain strong
Earlier on l had already warned you
Spiritual doctrines require total
determination
How could you leave monastery
at own will?
Not everyone can cultivate to be a Taoist
Fortune favours only a few
Why do you bear a grudge?
l know l'm wrong and willing to repent
l hope you could take me as
a disciple again
Yu Yuan Gi repenting her mistake
ln July of 7th year of Han Tung
She rejoins to the monastery
Lu Chiao
According to the written records,
lf you take this concoction
for thirty days
...your body will be light as a feather
lf you take it for forty nine days...
then you can be a divine being
Miss, please don't take anymore
Didn't you wish that we both become
celestial beings?
No, Miss
Miss...
Chang An's Ping Kang Lane is full of
singsong houses
3,000 households lean on the curtain
ln the brothels on the main avenue...
every girl is as beautiful as
a piece ofjade
How strange!
Hey, it's Yu Yuan Gi
Yes
Yes, that literary lady
Come over here, come
Why is she in Ping Kang Lane?
A crystal clear mirror with such
a fine pattern!
l've been everywhere in
Ping Kang Lane
...but haven't seen such a
beautiful mirror
Lu Chiao, do you mind if l use
your place to have my
...mirror polished?
Sure, no problem
Thank you
Chang, you come once a month
lf you don't come,
my lady will have no mirror
Right, have this polished...
Could you please...
Okay, put it down...
Miss Lu Chiao...
ls the lady of your house
...Miss Yu Yuan Gi?
Yes
The ladies in Ping Kang Lane...
are either procuresses or courtesans
We've fallen low having no other way out
But what about your lady?
She is a gifted scholar!
Yes...
That's right...so what's the reason?
So please do tell us the reason
Does the poetess Yu take things too hard?
Mirrors polished, washed and patched here
Miss
Only by softly touching your own mirror
would the beloved of your heart...
hear your words deep inside
Really?
Oh right, l've found your favourite flower
lt's so beautiful
You stick some too
No
Come on
Here, look
Come, sit down
Yu Yuan Gi
...everyone eagerly awaits your company
l have to pretend being a horse
Alright...
l'll take you as a stallion
You've already dressed up as a man
You'll be everyone's delight
Good, good
He is Taoist Yung of the Lung Sai family
He is totally dedicated
and seldom socialises
He's made an exception to be here...
because he wants to make your acquaintance
You're too kind
Although l'm always flanked by girls...
my heart is clear as a mirror
Good. This calls for a toast
Yuan Gi, we are both Taoist
When can we discuss the practises
of our doctrines?
You are from the orthodox school
...while l have been expelled
Are you afraid...l'll lead you astray?
Good...
Good
ls it hot?
Those 'charcoals' you brought
...are really terrific
What do you mean by 'charcoals'?
Female pimps who control the prostitutes
They curse and beat a girl up...
like a piece of crackling log on fire
Taoist Priest Yung, you've been
here all night...
just observing these activities;
why have you come?
Yuan Gi, l've come to admire your talent
...not to indulge in sensual pleasures
Come, let's drink...
Since you are insensitive to such
...mundane pleasures
Come...have a drink
Come...l'll scorch you
Come, come here...
lsn't that fun? They have feelings, too
...yet they're used to such treatment
ln this place...
all are treated equally
Man can play games on women
...and vice versa
Go and enjoy yourselves!
Come, scorch him, strip his clothes
Come here
You come over here
Come!
What a nuisance!
Miss
l found this while l was cleaning just now
lt bears the name of Taoist Yung
Splendid. He delivers us some money
just when...
we need it desperately
Good...
This wine is from a Persian friend
l never thought you were so good
lt's just luck
Talking of playing polo
...it's still a man's world
Thank you for being so generous
A pity, this isn't a whorehouse though!
So l should not accept your money
l wonder how a single lady...
can afford to live so extravagantly
every night
Right!
Men don't believe
that a woman can live alone
...and enjoy her life
How long do you think your savings
will last?
Don't worry, after all this splendour...
l'll retire to the simple life
lf you want to become a recluse,
why let all men in Chang An...
witness your splendour and grace?
l might want someone to become
a recluse with me
Made by Auyang the sword maker?
You know swords as well as you do the pen
Who is he?
The best sword maker around here
Where does he live?
Shih Li slope. East suburb of Chang An
Since that heavy rainfall...
this is the second time l see you
l haven't seen Tsui for a long time
lt's you l'm looking for...
need you to make a sword
What kind of a sword?
Not one...l need a pair
Of what length?
Say, three feet by ancient standard
And how wide?
4 inches
Any particular style?
Like a couple in loving embrace
l have to taste the owner's blood
...to ascertain the quality of the sword
My blood also contains Pok Hau's blood
Everywhere there is unrest
& aftermath of war
Pok Hau, l've no idea where you might be!
l feel terribly sorry...
for having to bother you
lt was necessary
You have a mild touch of the flu
But your cold waist and feet are
anaemia symptoms
And it's difficult to cure you
You drink too much
...and have overindulged in sex
l think you should retire
as soon as possible
...and focus on spiritual discipline
Alright!
But l need a man to accompany me
One who can respect me and...
who can accommodate my lifestyle;
To accompany me in retirement
Are you that man?
Yuan Gi, such loose behaviour of yours...
makes you no different from
other courtesans
lf you think l'm a whore for being
with one l like,
then each time when you see me...
and you abstain from coming close;
Aren't you worse than a whore's customer?
l come because l admire your talent
But when l see your decadence,
l am determined to withstand
...the temptations of flesh
That in true sense is obtaining
enlightenment
Come, try out your mettle
There is a man who represses himself
like you
He is Auyang the sword maker
He is like a strong piece of steel
...while you're like a piece of
intricate jade;
One which easily breaks
Almost, let's go in!
Look, Miss Yu is here
Miss Yu
An acquaintance is marrying today
Come and join the fun
Yes, go on in. Come...
Alright!
Here's a toast to you
Hello, everybody
Miss Yu, please take a seat
Thank you
Miss Yu
What would you and Lu Chiao like to have?
Have San Li, it's famous
That's right
lt's a good wine; very soothing
Okay
Miss, how have you been?
Congratulations
Xiang Xi, why get married at this
early an age?
You're still so young
That's right
What are you doing?
Don't do that...
Where's your beloved?
He's picking me up tomorrow
Her husband comes from a wealthy family
Says who? Don't listen to her
ln fact he only has a few acres of land
Just an ordinary farmer
But he's a nice person
...and of a good character
On his second visit itself to
the brothel he...
offered money to redeem me
You have it all set then,
a bright future and all
Miss Xiang Xi, l really envy you
Good, a nice song that one...
Anyone in?
Master
These are tea leaves from Yi Hing
And this here is a roll of frost paper
The best quality for writing poetry
This is a brocade vest
...for your birthday
These are socks from Soo Chau
Especially apt for your smooth skin
The brocade is lined with silk inside out
Even more free & easy without it all!
Li, you are an honest merchant
l'm an oft rumoured profligate woman
You shouldn't let this gossip...
bother you. Only...
lf you come back, l...
l wouldn't care about anything else
Think about it again
Splash! Splash!
What happened to you?
Why do you have bruises all over?
My man beat me up
By day he wants me to be good
And by night he wants me to be bad
Saying, the worse the better
Aren't you going to participate?
l have to hold the clothes for miss,
how about you?
Hey, where are these refugees from?
l am not sure
Of late there've been a series of
uprisings by farmers
After one unrest is over, the...
roving bandits bring up
yet another calamity
What a shame!
Refugees...
Can any household give me shelter?
Excuse please, make way
Listen, you all. Come to my place
There's food and lodging
Whoever wants to be courtesan
come over here
Hurry up, lodge & board provided
Come over quickly...
The entire Ping Kang Lane is managed
by you
Girls in our brothel
are well taken care of...
Quick, come to my place...hurry up
Yuan Gi
l'll go back to get changed
You're coming tonight for a drink together
So get changed at my place
Lu Chiao, escort Taoist Yung back
Yes
Leave your fingerprints on the contract
Please put me up at your place...
l'll do anything
you say...l beg of you
Lu Chiao
Does Yuan Gi want to take them up
as maids?
Miss
Prepare some hot water
They haven't bathed for a long time
Yes
Where have you come from?
From Sheung Chau, quite far from Chang An
l hear the people there have put up
a rebellion
lnitially, yes
But then, even the soldiers
pillaged and killed
What was the reason for the uprising?
No farmland...there's not enough to eat
How else could one survive?
Sorry, we just finished a performance
elsewhere
...that's why we're late
Continue to play and sing
l'm also an art lover
l hear Yu Yuan Gi is talented
and beautiful
...and surrounded by many beauties
l've since long yearned for her
lsn't that right?
There are so many ladies here
l wonder which one is Miss Yu?
l am here. May l know your name?
How come so many other big-foot women
are here?
lt seems Poetess Yu only bears a name
Although a bit disappointing,
but she's still a woman
This is the capital of Tang
How dare you be insolent here?
Who are you all?
Me?
l am Kung Meng Wu
So Kung, the notorious killer of
corrupt officials,
turns out to be a dog!
A Dog?
What do you want?
Oh, there are many things l want
l would like to get laid...
and enjoy life as you people
And to use the convenient facilities here
Attack
You beast!
They are all farmers
...just like you
Why do you degrade yourself?
Nothing but a beast!
What?
Who are you to lecture me?
You people flirting with girl
call yourselves romantic
Yet if we do it, you call it degrading
l'll show you what is degrading
Drag her out
l hear you both get on very well
l'd actually like to experience some of it
What do you say?
Good!
Come!
Let go
Quickly, ask them to move it
Hurry up
Quickly
Don't cry
Come on!
Miss, l desire to go back home
lsn't this your own home?
l mean, return to my hometown
Kung Meng W
You incite the farmers to rebel
...and you take the opportunity to pillage
l, Tsui Pok Hau,
must do away today with a
bandit dog like you
l, Auyang the sword maker,
must take your head today
Lu Chiao
Miss
Kill him
So, what have you done...
these two years?
Wandering everywhere
Killed how many?
l don't remember
And how many female bodies 'borrowed'?
l have lost count
You and Auyang claim yourselves
to be heroes
...killing thugs and traitors
Say, would you dare kill an evil emperor?
l'd kill the same way
What have you been doing
the past two years?
l don't remember
Hey, this winter...
l'll hold a wine and poetry function
in the courtyard
lt must be enjoyable
Lu Chiao must be becoming intelligent,
following such a literary talent...
with an increasing fame like you
Lu Chiao is my only personal companion
l hope she is happy the rest of her life
lf you had not pursued that
bandit Kung here
...would you have looked me up?
You have too many visitors
...including the chief of bandits
Not really. ln fact, l was bent on
looking for a man
What...scared you, did l?
l am not in the mood for a man today
Miss, the sword maker is here
l have made the swords you ordered
How many times have you refined it?
A hundred
Have you tried them?
Yes
How many strings has it broken?
Fifteen
What's all the string talk?
Using hair strands to tie up straw pieces
...to test out the sharp edge
Of these both, which one is sharper?
l shall appreciate having a demonstration
Certainly the best you've ever made
Yuan Gi asked me to make them for you
These swords are a gift to
you both great heroes
Please go and tidy up the guest room
Yes
What does Lu Chiao want with you?
Said she's thinking to settle down
Miss
Hey, come down and play with us
Come down quickly...don't be so stubborn
Come and enjoy...
No, don't
Come, join us
Please don't
Don't run away, come...
Please stay...
Why do you just sneak around with Yuan Gi
...and don't play with us?
Come...come on...
Recently l'm going through a
writer's block
...and can't write poems as l used to
You must be having too much sex and wine
Such a beauty!
Yet so clumsy in pouring wine
Mr Chang, you're right
Lu Chiao, come and drink with us
Lu Chiao, please sit
See? Even Miss Yu has asks you to sit
Come come, have a drink with us
Miss Yu
Please compose a poem for us to enjoy
Can you please?
Yes...
Sorry, l'm not in the mood
That can't be, Miss Yu
How much do you want me to pay for it?
Wan Bai Chai, is it true with each
eight rounds
...you can compose a poem?
Bai Chai was merely describing
his poetic talent
l'll use three rounds instead of eight
Really?
Li Shang Ran's line referred to a lute
with 50 strings
Doesn't make sense
A lute has twenty five strings only
Why did she say fifty strings?
Oh, you're a crackpot
Your lines 'lt's easier to acquire
a rare gem...
than to come by a true lover'...
are still the greatest
My mistress reads them to me every night
Since when are you so nice as to...
accompanying your pet concubine
every night?
Yi Shang passed away in a Cheng Chau
monastery
...a little over a month ago
How did it happen?
A friend from Cheng Chau said...
he lost his sight and died of dejection
Fei Hsiang also wrote from Wah Nan...
saying he has not changed his mad ways;
And ended up having two of his teeth
knocked off!
Fei is still so crazy and so likeable
She can't tolerate even a little wine
Lu Chiao, are you unwell?
lt's nothing
Go inside and rest
l'm fine
Well then, let's drink away
Do you need money?
Don't leave me any more money
l won't use it anyway
l want to depend on myself
Being a girl does come in helpful at times
Finally...l get to hear your moaning
at least!
What, you're going to leave it at that?
C'mon, get up and see me out
Miss, l'm so sorry
l couldn't get up in time
Are you feeling a little better?
l'm alright
Lu Chiao, are you pregnant by any chance?
ls it Pok Hau's?
Or Fei Hsiang?
Or Taoist Yung?
So even you don't know it!
lf the child belongs to those bandits
...you sure can tell me
No
Take some medicine and get rid of it
No miss, l won't
l want to return to my hometown
After giving birth, l'll marry
With whom?
With Tsui Pok Hau?
No
Miss, presently l'm saving money
What for?
To redeem myself
Redeem yourself?
lf you want to go
l can let you go any time
l have treated you like my baby sister
Why do you speak of redeeming...
and regard yourself so lowly?
No
Actually one can live freely without...
having to marry or bear children
...and solely depending on a man!
No, l've been born as a girl slave
...not so casual & elegant as you
You are a GlRL, not a maid
Who has made you like this?
Tell me, who?
This medicine is for abortion
Now be good and take it
You have followed me for a long time
l don't want to see you ruin yourself
...nor see you leave
lf you leave, l'll kill you
l know you can kill me
You are the Lady, l'm a maid
No
-You're not a maid
-l am
You are a girl
l have never treated you like a maid
l am
-You're not a maid
-l am
You're not...
There aren't too many happy days
in one's life
Right?
l wish to buy back Lu Chiao's freedom
You're cultivated according to
religious doctrines
What do you want her for?
l want to let her return to her hometown
Your lifestyle doesn't suit her
Shall appreciate if we could discuss
her price
What price?
l have never treated her like a maid
Why should there be any price?
l've already let her return to
her hometown
She's gone to get married
Yes, maestro...what is it?
l would like to meet Miss Lu
What do you want with her?
l...
l want to tell her that...
l have saved up 20 taels of silver
l wonder if that's enough to redeem her
She's gone back to her hometown
to get married
May l ask when she'd be back?
l have saved up 20 taels of silver for her
She's gone to get married,
how would she return?
Really, so many guys like Lu Chiao
And struggle to want her
So many men desire you, too
But you reject them
Lu Chiao was born...
for belonging to you men
l'm not that kind of a woman
l...sort of belong only to myself
Look at you, sitting there you look
so coquettish
Lying down you'll be all the more luring
How about teaching some of it all
to Chau Yuet?
Last night when l was in bed with her...
oh boy, she was so stiff!
Come and drink this potion
They say you're quite strange,
but l wouldn't say so
You all must be thirsty.
Here, please have this
Miss, it smells so awful here,
what could it be?
Yes...
lt's a dreadful stench
What are you talking about?
lt's so fragrant!
Miss, what's your name?
Lu Chiao
This...
Hey look
Lu Chiao is dead, her body is buried here
Come and look!
Lu Chiao, Lu Chiao...
Hurry up you both, okay!
Yes...sure
Haven't yet stripped her?
Be quick
l'm here, too
Come on
Me first
lt should be me
Your Taoist admirer turned out
real sentimental!
Guess he couldn't bear to see you arrested
...so he killed himself!
He has been bleeding for over a day
Many scholars have jointly petitioned
...for your pardon
Yin Wen Chang however is of
the opinion that:
Although you have a brilliant mind...
your ways are unacceptable
And reckons you ought to be beheaded
without delay
l know your executioner has a swift hand
Your pain will only be momentary;
My sword is quicker than him
lf you let me kill you now...
your suffering will be even shorter
You want to kill me with your own hands
How pretentious of you!
My heartfelt gratitude, great hero
l won't let your kind go easily satisfied
Hey, will Pok Hau return?
Would he ever?
This place is guarded so heavily
Whoever comes, it's of no use
Let's go
Come on, please
You come and go as you wish
Have you ever asked me what l want?
Well, what do you want?
Are you coming or not?
l won't
Yuan Gi, why weren't you prepared
to leave?
l've beaten many tracks other women
wouldn't dare
And don't feel up to it anymore!
Pok Hau, why didn't you continue
to be a drifter?
l'd have loved roaming about with you
Without you though, it's meaningless
l'll accompany you in death instead
Feel loath getting up...
in dreary spring to apply make-up
lt's easier to acquire priceless treasure
...than to come by a true lover!
ln May, the 9th year of Han Tung's reign,
Auyang the sword maker killed...
the Hero Tsui Pok Hau and...
Yu Yuan Gi, the literary talent of
Chang An!